Guide to the Otto Eisenlohr Rice Institute letters, 1915-1921 MS 536
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Otto Eisenlohr Rice Institute letters
1915-1921
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Eisenlohr, Otto, -1988
MS 536
5 Linear Feet (10 boxes)
Correspondence from Rice Institute student Otto Eisenlohr to his high school sweetheart and eventual wife, Gainor Roberts, regarding student life, academics and athletics at Rice Institute, and contemporary newsclippings and photographs.
(10 boxes)
Biographical Note
Otto Eisenlohr (d. 1988) of Dallas, Texas, attended Rice Institute from 1915 to 1921, and graduated in 1921. Eisenlohr attended medical school and practiced medicine in Dallas. He married Gainor Roberts of Dallas in 1920, and after her death in 1938, married Nell Vaughn in 1942.
Scope and Contents
Correspondence from Rice Institute student Otto Eisenlohr to his high school sweetheart and eventual wife, Gainor Roberts, regarding student life, academics and athletics at Rice Institute, and contemporary newsclippings and photographs.
Topics include Rice during the First World War, Houston from 1915-1921, science at Rice Institute, hazing of freshmen by upperclassmen, secret societies on campus, popular movies, dances, Rice football, basketball, and baseball, and ROTC activities during the first World War.
Access Restrictions
This material is open for research.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored onsite at the Woodson Research Center.
Acquisition Information
This collection was a gift donated by Otto's son John Eisenlohr in Dec. 2007. These letters were discovered by John Eisenlohr in the attic of his father's home at 1042 Lausanne, Dallas, Texas, in 2002, when the house was cleaned out before its sale.
General Note
Portions of this collection are available online at: https://scholarship.rice.edu/handle/1911/26498" title="Otto Eisenlohr Rice Institute letters">https://scholarship.rice.edu/handle/1911/26498
Index Terms
Subjects
Social life and customs; Rice University -- History; Universities and colleges
Document Types
corrrespondence
Subjects (Persons)
Eisenlohr, Otto, -1988; Roberts, Gainor
- Series I: 1915, 247624
  - 06/25/1915 (5 pgs.), 247628 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 09/27/1915 (8 pgs.), 247627 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 10/11/1915 (5 pgs.), 247626 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 12/05/1915 (5 pgs.), 247625 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Series II: 1916, 247578
  - 01/01/1916 (3 pgs.), 247623 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 01/04/1916 (4 pgs.), 247622 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 01/08/1916 (5 pgs.), 247621 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 01/15/1916 (5 pgs.) -- Food fight, 247620 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 01/22/1916 (5 pgs.) -- Military training, 247619 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 01/29/1916 (4 pgs.), 247618 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 02/07/1916 (5 pgs.), 247617 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 02/13/1916 (6 pgs.), 247616 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 02/16/1916 (4 pgs.), 247615 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 02/19/1916 (4 pgs.), 247614 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 02/26/1916 (7 pgs.) -- Gun prank involving guard, 247613 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 03/04/1916 (4 pgs.), 247612 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 03/12/1916 (4 pgs.), 247611 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 03/23/1916 (4 pgs.), 247610 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 03/31/1916 (4 pgs.), 247609 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 04/08/1916 (7 pgs.), 247608 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 04/17/1916 (5 pgs.), 247607 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 04/21/1916 (4 pgs.), 247606 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 04/30/1916 (4 pgs.), 247605 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 05/08/1916 (4 pgs.), 247604 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 05/18/1916 (8 pgs.), 247603 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 05/28/1916 (4 pgs.), 247602 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 07/16/1916 (4 pgs.), 247601 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 07/22/1916 (4 pgs.), 247600 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 07/29/1916 (4 pgs.), 247599 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 08/05/1916 (6 pgs.), 247598 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 08/12/1916 (9 pgs.) -- Race relations in Houston, Texas-Rice Football rivalry, 247597 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 08/13/1916 (5 pgs.), 247596 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 08/19/1916 (5 pgs.), 247595 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 09/17/1916 (9 pgs.), 247594 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 09/21/1916 (12 pgs.) Ships at Galveston Port, hostility toward English ship, 247593 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 09/29/1916 (10 pgs.) 300 New freshmen, 247592 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 10/06/1916 (7 pgs.) -- Elected Sophomore Class President, 247591 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 10/13/1916 (6 pgs.) -- List of Freshman "Laws", 247590 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 10/20/1916 (7 pgs.) -- Prank locking Freshmen in room, 247589 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 10/24/1916 (3 pgs.), 247588 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 10/25/1916 (7 pgs.) -- Students attempt to ban hazing of Freshmen, 247587 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 10/30/1916 (7 pgs.), 247586 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 11/04/1916 (10 pgs.) -- Tied and blindfolded Freshmen, 247585 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 11/11/1916 (7 pgs.), 247584 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 11/19/1916 (7 pgs.), 247583 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 11/26/1916 (7 pgs.), 247582 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 12/03/1916 (7 pgs.), 247581 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 12/09/1916 (4 pgs.), 247580 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 12/16/1916 (6 pgs.), 247579 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Series III: 1917, 247522
  - 01/04/1917 (7 pgs.), 247577 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 01/08/1917 (7 pgs.) -- Austrian and German ships Interned at Galveston, 247576 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 01/12/1917 (7 pgs.) -- Secret Society at Rice, 247575 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 01/17/1917 (7 pgs.), 247574 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 01/20/1917 (4 pgs.), 247573 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 01/21/1917 (7 pgs.), 247572 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 01/25/1917 (6 pgs.), 247571 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 01/30/1917 (7 pgs.), 247570 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 02/04/1917 (10 pgs.) -- Texas A&M steals owl, Rice steals it back, shots fired, 247569 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 02/08/1917 (7 pgs.) -- Texas A&M steals donkey, Rice recovers, Discussion of War, German background, 247568 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 02/12/1917 (7 pgs.) -- Airship near campus, 247567 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 02/16/1917 (5 pgs.) -- Considering returning home, 247566 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 02/20/1917 (5 pgs.), 247565 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 02/25/1917 (9 pgs.), 247564 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 03/01/1917 (5 pgs.), 247563 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 03/05/1917 (5 pgs.), 247562 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 03/09/1917 (5 pgs.), 247561 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 03/15/1917 (5 pgs.) -- Exams, a ride in a Car, prank on Freshmen, 247560 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 03/19/1917 (5 pgs.), 247559 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 03/23/1917 (5 pgs.), 247558 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 03/28/1917 (5 pgs.) -- Naval Destroyers Arrive, Baseball season, Death of English instructor, 247557 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 04/01/1917 (5 pgs.), 247556 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 04/06/1917 (5 pgs.) -- Possible Conscription, Lovett mandates military training, 247555 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 04/09/1917 (5 pgs.) -- Discussion of enlisting in hospital Corps, 247554 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 04/13/1917 (5 pgs.), 247553 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 04/18/1917 (5 pgs.), 247552 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 04/22/1917 (7 pgs.) -- Junior Prom, Picnic, controversy over water thrown by students, 247551 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 04/26/1917 (7 pgs.), 247550 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 05/01/1917 (7 pgs.) -- Officer Camp at Leon Springs, Students leaving for service, Enlisting, Lovett's farewell speech to students leaving for war, 247549 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 05/06/1917 (7 pgs.) -- Passed military physical, Fell asleep in class, 50 Students leaving for military Training, 247548 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 05/10/1917 (7 pgs.), 247547 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 05/14/1917 (7 pgs.), 247546 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 05/22/1917 (7 pgs.) -- Strapping of Freshmen for Dress Code Violations, "Sacking" freshmen, freshmen vs. freshmen wars, 247545 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 05/26/1917 (9 pgs.) -- Food fight over quality of meals, Repainting of dining hall, Short suspension, 247544 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 05/31/1917 (7 pgs.), 247543 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 06/05/1917 (6 pgs.), 247542 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 09/21/1917 (8 pgs.), 247541 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 09/27/1917 (9 pgs.), 247540 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 10/02/1917 (8 pgs.) -- Description of ranks and uniforms on campus, 247539 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 10/06/1917 (7 pgs.), 247538 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 10/11/1917 (7 pgs.), 247537 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 10/15/1917 (7 pgs.), 247536 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 10/19/1917 (7 pgs.), 247535 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 10/25/1917 (8 pgs.), 247534 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 10/30/1917 (9 pgs.), 247533 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 11/04/1917 (9 pgs.), 247532 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 11/09/1917 (6 pgs.), 247531 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 11/15/1917 (7 pgs.), 247530 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 11/18/1917 (8 pgs.) -- Dissatisfaction in ROTC, 247529 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 11/21/1917 (8 pgs.), 247528 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 11/27/1917 (3 pgs.), 247527 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 12/05/1917 (7 pgs.), 247526 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - 12/08/1917 (6 pgs.), 247525 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - 12/13/1917 (8 pgs.), 247524 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - 12/18/1917 (5 pgs.), 247523 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Series IV: 1918, 247424
  - 01/03/1918 (5 pgs.), 247521 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 01/07/1918 (7 pgs.), 247520 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 01/11/1918 (7 pgs.), 247519 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 01/15/1918 (10 pgs.), 247518 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 01/19/1918 (10 pgs.), 247517 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 01/24/1918 (10 pgs.), 247516 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 01/29/1918 (12 pgs.), 247515 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 02/01/1918 (9 pgs.), 247514 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 02/02/1918 (12 pgs.), 247513 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 02/08/1918 (9 pgs.), 247512 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 02/12/1918 (15 pgs.), 247511 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 02/13/1918 (3 pgs.), 247510 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 02/18/1918 (7 pgs.), 247509 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 02/20/1918 (7 pgs.), 247508 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 02/26/1918 (9 pgs.), 247507 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 03/02/1918 (9 pgs.), 247506 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 03/07/1918 (9 pgs.), 247505 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 03/12/1918 (9 pgs.), 247504 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 03/19/1918 (9 pgs.), 247503 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 03/22/1918 (9 pgs.), 247502 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 03/26/1918 (8 pgs.), 247501 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 03/30/1918 (6 pgs.), 247500 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 04/04/1918 (6 pgs.), 247499 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 04/09/1918 (5 pgs.), 247498 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 04/12/1918 (5 pgs.), 247497 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 04/16/1918 (5 pgs.), 247496 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 04/19/1918 (8 pgs.), 247495 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 04/23/1918 (7 pgs.), 247494 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 04/26/1918 (7 pgs.), 247493 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 04/30/1918 (7 pgs.), 247492 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 05/03/1918 (2 pgs.), 247491 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 05/07/1918 (5 pgs.), 247490 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 05/10/1918 (4 pgs.), 247489 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 05/14/1918 (9 pgs.), 247488 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 05/17/1918 (10 pgs.), 247487 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 05/21/1918 (8 pgs.), 247486 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 05/24/1918 (9 pgs.), 247485 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 05/28/1918 (6 pgs.), 247484 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 06/01/1918 (7 pgs.), 247483 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 06/12/1918 (9 pgs.), 247482 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 06/16/1918 (14 pgs.), 247481 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 06/19/1918 (14 pgs.), 247480 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 06/23/1918 (11 pgs.), 247479 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 06/26/1918 (11 pgs.), 247478 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 06/30/1918 (11 pgs.), 247477 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 07/05/1918 (10 pgs), 247476 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 07/08/1918 (9 pgs), 247475 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 07/11/1918 (12 pgs), 247474 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 07/15/1918 (8 pgs), 247473 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 07/18/1918 (9 pgs), 247472 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 07/21/1918 (17 pgs), 247471 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 07/24/1918 (10 pgs), 247470 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 07/27/1918 (9 pgs), 247469 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 07/30/1918 (8 pgs), 247468 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 08/02/1918 (8 pgs.), 247467 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 08/05/1918 (6 pgs.), 247466 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 08/08/1918 (8 pgs.), 247465 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 08/10/1918 (9 pgs.), 247464 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 08/12/1918 (8 pgs.), 247463 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 08/22/1918 (4 pgs.), 247462 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 08/22/1918 (b) (4 pgs.), 247461 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 08/22/1918 (c) (4 pgs.), 247460 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 08/24/1918 (3 pgs.), 247459 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 08/30/1918 (5 pgs.), 247458 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 09/03/1918 (6 pgs.), 247457 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 09/04/1918 (4 pgs.), 247456 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 09/08/1918 (4 pgs.), 247455 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 09/11/1918 (7 pgs.), 247454 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 09/14/1918 (5 pgs.), 247453 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 09/16/1918 (4 pgs.), 247452 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 09/16/1918 (b) (9 pgs.), 247451 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 09/18/1918 (6 pgs.), 247450 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 09/23/1918 (6 pgs.), 247449 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 09/26/1918 (4 pgs.), 247448 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 09/30/1918 (7 pgs.), 247447 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 10/04/1918 (5 pgs.), 247446 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 10/06/1918 (3 pgs.), 247445 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 10/12/1918 (3 pgs.), 247444 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 10/17/1918 (5 pgs.), 247443 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 10/19/1918 (7 pgs.), 247442 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 10/24/1918 (9 pgs.), 247441 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 10/28/1918 (7 pgs.), 247440 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 10/30/1918 (6 pgs.), 247439 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 11/01/1918 (7 pgs.), 247438 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - 11/04/1918 (5 pgs.), 247437 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - 11/07/1918 (4 pgs.), 247436 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - 11/09/1918 (5 pgs.), 247435 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - 11/18/1918 (5 pgs.), 247434 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - 11/19/1918 (10 pgs.), 247433 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Undated Newspaper Clippings (1914-1918), 247432 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Undated Photographs (1914-1918), 247431 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Undated Letter 1 (1914-1918), 247430 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Undated Letter 2 (1914-1918), 247429 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Undated Letter 3 (1914-1918), 247428 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Undated Letter 4 (1914-1918), 247427 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Undated Card 1 (1914-1918), 247426 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Undated Card 2 (1914-1918), 247425 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Series V: 1919, 247371
  - 08/02/1919 (10 pgs.), 247423 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 08/04/1919 (10 pgs.), 247422 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 08/04/1919 (b) (10 pgs.), 247421 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 08/06/1919 (9 pgs.), 247420 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 08/08/1919 (8 pgs.), 247419 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 08/08/1919 (b) (9 pgs.), 247418 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 09/20/1919 (9 pgs.), 247417 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 09/21/1919 (6 pgs.), 247416 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 09/23/1919 (4 pgs.), 247415 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 09/25/1919 (9 pgs.), 247414 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 09/27/1919 (10 pgs.), 247413 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 09/30/1919 (11 pgs.), 247412 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 10/01/1919 (8 pgs.), 247411 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 10/04/1919 (12 pgs), 247410 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 10/05/1919 (8 pgs), 247409 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 10/08/1919 (10 pgs), 247408 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 10/09/1919 (7 pgs), 247407 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 10/14/1919 (9 pgs), 247406 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 10/15/1919 (8 pgs), 247405 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 10/16/1919 (8 pgs), 247404 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 10/18/1919 (9 pgs), 247403 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 10/19/1919 (9 pgs), 247402 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 10/21/1919 (11 pgs), 247401 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 10/22/1919 (8 pgs), 247400 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 10/23/1919 (9 pgs), 247399 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 10/25/1919 (9 pgs), 247398 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 10/28/1919 (9 pgs), 247397 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 10/29/1919 (6 pgs), 247396 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 11/04/1919 (9 pgs), 247395 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 11/05/1919 (7 pgs), 247394 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 11/08/1919 (11 pgs), 247393 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 11/09/1919 (8 pgs), 247392 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 11/11/1919 (8 pgs), 247391 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 11/13/1919 (8 pgs), 247390 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 11/14/1919 (6 pgs), 247389 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 11/15/1919 (10 pgs), 247388 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 11/18/1919 (8 pgs), 247387 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 11/20/1919 (9 pgs), 247386 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 11/22/1919 (15 pgs), 247385 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 11/25/1919 (6 pgs), 247384 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 12/02/1919 (9 pgs), 247383 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 12/02/1919 (b) (8 pgs), 247382 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 12/05/1919 (9 pgs), 247381 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 12/06/1919 (14 pgs), 247380 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 12/09/1919 (8 pgs), 247379 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 12/09/1919 (b) (8 pgs), 247378 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 12/10/1919 (8 pgs), 247377 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 12/11/1919 (8 pgs), 247376 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 12/14/1919 (15 pgs), 247375 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 12/15/1919 (8 pgs), 247374 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 12/17/1919 (7 pgs), 247373 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 12/19/1919 (7 pgs), 247372 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Series VI: 1920, 247252
  - 01/03/1920 (6 pgs), 247370 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 01/04/1920 (6 pgs), 247369 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 01/05/1920 (9 pgs), 247368 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 01/07/1920 (6 pgs), 247367 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 01/10/1920 (13 pgs), 247366 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 01/11/1920 (6 pgs), 247365 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 01/15/1920 (6 pgs), 247364 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 01/16/1920 (6 pgs), 247363 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 01/17/1920 (12 pgs), 247362 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 01/19/1920 (8 pgs), 247361 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 01/20/1920 (8 pgs), 247360 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 01/21/1920 (8 pgs), 247359 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 01/22/1920 (8 pgs), 247358 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 01/23/1920 (11 pgs), 247357 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 01/24/1920 (14 pgs), 247356 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 01/27/1920 (9 pgs), 247355 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 01/28/1920 (8 pgs), 247354 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 01/29/1920 (8 pgs), 247353 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 02/03/1920 (10 pgs), 247352 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 02/04/1920 (8 pgs), 247351 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 02/05/1920 (9 pgs), 247350 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 02/06/1920 (11 pgs), 247349 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 02/07/1920 (8 pgs), 247348 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 02/08/1920 (8 pgs), 247347 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 02/10/1920 (8 pgs), 247346 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 02/11/1920 (6 pgs), 247345 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 02/12/1920 (8 pgs), 247344 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 02/14/1920 (7 pgs), 247343 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 02/14/1920 (b) (7 pgs), 247342 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 02/14/1920 (c) (10 pgs), 247341 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 02/16/1920 (6 pgs), 247340 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 02/17/1920 (8 pgs), 247339 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 02/18/1920 (8 pgs), 247338 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 02/19/1920 (9 pgs), 247337 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 02/20/1920 (6 pgs), 247336 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 02/21/1920 (7 pgs), 247335 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 02/25/1920 (9 pgs), 247334 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 02/26/1920 (7 pgs), 247333 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 02/27/1920 (8 pgs), 247332 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 02/28/1920 (11 pgs), 247331 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 02/29/1920 (6 pgs), 247330 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 03/02/1920 (7 pgs), 247329 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 03/03/1920 (8 pgs), 247328 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 03/04/1920 (8 pgs), 247327 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 03/06/1920 (9 pgs), 247326 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 03/07/1920 (8 pgs), 247325 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 03/10/1920 (9 pgs), 247324 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 03/13/1920 (17 pgs), 247323 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 03/15/1920 (8 pgs), 247322 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 03/16/1920 (9 pgs), 247321 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 03/18/1920 (6 pgs), 247320 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 03/19/1920 (8 pgs), 247319 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 03/20/1920 (9 pgs), 247318 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 03/23/1920 (11 pgs), 247317 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 03/24/1920 (8 pgs), 247316 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 03/26/1920 (6 pgs), 247315 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 03/27/1920 (9 pgs), 247314 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 03/30/1920 (8 pgs), 247313 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 03/31/1920 (6 pgs), 247312 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 03/31/1920 (b) (6 pgs), 247311 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 04/03/1920 (10 pgs), 247310 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 04/04/1920 (6 pgs), 247309 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 04/07/1920 (8 pgs), 247308 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 04/08/1920 (11 pgs), 247307 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 04/10/1920 (9 pgs), 247306 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 04/13/1920 (10 pgs), 247305 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 04/14/1920 (9 pgs), 247304 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 04/15/1920 (8 pgs), 247303 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 04/17/1920 (14 pgs), 247302 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 04/18/1920 (9 pgs), 247301 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 04/20/1920 (9 pgs), 247300 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 04/23/1920 (8 pgs), 247299 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 04/24/1920 (8 pgs), 247298 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 04/24/1920 (b) (10 pgs), 247297 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 04/25/1920 (10 pgs), 247296 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 04/27/1920 (8 pgs), 247295 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 04/28/1920 (8 pgs), 247294 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 04/29/1920 (8 pgs), 247293 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 05/01/1920 (11 pgs), 247292 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 05/04/1920 (8 pgs), 247291 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 05/05/1920 (7 pgs), 247290 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 05/07/1920 (8 pgs), 247289 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 05/08/1920 (12 pgs), 247288 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 05/09/1920 (7 pgs), 247287 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 05/11/1920 (8 pgs), 247286 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 05/12/1920 (7 pgs), 247285 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 05/13/1920 (9 pgs), 247284 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 05/15/1920 (12 pgs), 247283 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 05/17/1920 (7 pgs), 247282 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 05/18/1920 (8 pgs), 247281 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 05/19/1920 (8 pgs), 247280 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 05/21/1920 (9 pgs), 247279 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 05/21/1920 (b) (10 pgs), 247278 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 05/22/1920 (10 pgs), 247277 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 05/23/1920 (6 pgs), 247276 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 05/25/1920 (7 pgs), 247275 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 05/28/1920 (7 pgs), 247274 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 05/29/1920 (6 pgs), 247273 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 06/01/1920 (6 pgs), 247272 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 08/18/1920 (4 pgs), 247271 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 08/19/1920 (3 pgs), 247270 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 08/20/1920 (3 pgs), 247269 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 09/24/1920 (3 pgs), 247268 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 11/20/1920 (5 pgs), 247267 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 11/20/1920 (b) (4 pgs), 247266 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 12/04/1920 (6 pgs), 247265 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 12/07/1920 (7 pgs), 247264 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 12/09/1920 (7 pgs), 247263 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 12/10/1920 (7 pgs), 247262 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 12/11/1920 (10 pgs), 247261 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 12/12/1920 (6 pgs), 247260 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 12/13/1920 (7 pgs), 247259 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 12/14/1920 (7 pgs), 247258 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 12/15/1920 (7 pgs), 247257 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 12/16/1920 (6 pgs), 247256 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 12/17/1920 (9 pgs), 247255 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 12/18/1920 (7 pgs), 247254 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 12/19/1920 (8 pgs), 247253 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Series VII: 1921, 247243
  - 03/09/1921 (7 pgs), 247251 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - 03/10/1921 (5 pgs), 247250 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Undated Exam (1919-1921) (21 pgs), 247249 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Undated Newspaper Clippings (1919-1921), 247248 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Undated Photographs (1919-1921) (2 pgs), 247247 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Undated Letter (1919-1921) (8 pgs), 247246 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Undated Card 1 (1919-1921) (1 pg), 247245 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Undated Card 2 (1919-1921) (6 pgs), 247244 (Box 10, Folder 3)